Register to The Leroy Anderson Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, Series I
  - Music of Leroy Anderson, The (Vol. 1) Mills Music Inc., c1961 (Box 12, Folder 408)
    7 copies. Collection includes: "Blue Tango", "Promenade", "Syncopated Clock", "Song of the Bells", "Forgotten Dreams", "The First Day of Spring", "Saraband", and "The Phantom Regiment".
  - Music of Leroy Anderson, The (Vol. 1) Mills Music Inc., c1962 (Box 12, Folder 409)
  - Music of Leroy Anderson, The (Vol. 1) Mills Music Inc., c1962 (Box 12, Folder 411)
  - Music of Leroy Anderson, The (Vol. 1) Mills Music Inc., c1961 (Box 12, Folder 412)
    arr. Mel Bay
  - Musical Jukebox Cromwell Music, c1950; score (23 p.) (Box 12, Folder 415)
    "Piano part added 1/1/59."
    Includes letter from Leroy Anderson to Mr. L.J. Rodgers, Symphony Hall, Boston dated 4/22/50. "Recorded 21 June 1950 by Arthur Fiedler."
  - Musik von Leroy Anderson Band 2 Mills Musikverlag, score (55 p.) (Box 12, Folder 416)
    Collection of 12 compositions. German edition.
  - Musik von Leroy Anderson Heft 1 Mills Musikverlag, score (58 p.) (Box 12, Folder 417)
  - My Romance, 11/5/35; score (4 p.) (Box 12, Folder 418)
  - Nancy's Waltzes, 11/4/38; score (6 p.) (Box 12, Folder 419)
  - Never a Day, score (4 p.) (Box 12, Folder 420)
  - Never Again, condensed score (3 p.) & parts (Box 12, Folder 421)
    Anne Dennett Blyth
  - Never Say Never Again, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 12, Folder 422)
    Pencil. Alto sax 1 and 3 parts are on reverse side of score.
  - Niagara, score (3 p.) (Box 12, Folder 423)
  - Nice Work If You Can Get It, score (1 p.) (Box 12, Folder 424)
  - Nights of Gladness/Two Hearts, 10/10/40; score (11 p.) (Box 12, Folder 425)
  - Now Love Has Gone Away, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 12, Folder 426)
  - Obvious, score (3 p.) (Box 12, Folder 427)
  - Old Flame Never Dies, An, score (4 p.) (Box 12, Folder 428)
  - Old Folks at Home (sketch), condensed score (2 p.) (Box 25, Folder 871)
  - Old MacDonald Had a Farm., score (p. 1-13 only) (Box 25, Folder 872)
    photocopy of holograph
  - Old MacDonald Had a Farm (sketch), 4/7/47; condensed score (8 p.) (Box 25, Folder 873)
  - Old Man River, 12/19/48; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 12, Folder 429)
  - On Wings of Song (sketch), condensed score (3 p.) (Box 25, Folder 874)
  - One Alone, 1/16/49; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 12, Folder 430)
  - Orange and the Black, score (1 p.) (Box 12, Folder 431)
  - Oriental Scarf Dance, score (13 p.) (Box 12, Folder 432)
    Peggy Stuart
  - Our Director/Washington Post, 10/10/40; score (11 p.) (Box 12, Folder 433)
  - Out of the Night, score (5 p.) (Box 12, Folder 434)
  - Pack Up Your Troubles/Keep the Home Fires Burning, score (4 p.) (Box 12, Folder 435)
  - Pathétique, score (1 p.) & parts (Box 12, Folder 436)
    P.I. Tchaikovsky
    Pencil. For 1935 Vincent Club show. Based on a theme from Tchaikovsky's Sixth Symphony.
  - Pathétique Waltz, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 26, Folder 437)
  - Patter, score (3 p.) (Box 12, Folder 438)
  - Penny Whistle Song, The Mills Music Ltd., c1953; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 12, Folder 439)
  - Penny-Whistle Song, The, 6/3/51; score (16 p.) (Box 12, Folder 440)
  - Penny-Whistle Song, The Mills Music Ltd., c1951; score (6 p.) (Box 12, Folder 441)
  - Penny-Whistle Song, The Mills Music Inc./Belwin Mills, c1959; score (7 p.) & parts (Box 13, Folder 442)
    3 flutes & piano
  - Penny-Whistle Song, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (5 p.) (Box 13, Folder 443)
  - Penny-Whistle Song, The Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (5 p.) (Box 13, Folder 444)
  - Penny-Whistle Song, The Mills Music Inc., c1953; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 13, Folder 445)
  - Penny-Whistle Song, The Mills Music Inc., c1955; score (16 p.), condensed score (6 p.) & parts (Box 13, Folder 446)
  - Penny-Whistle Song, The, 10/25/54; score (17 p.) (Box 25, Folder 875)
  - Penny-Whistle Song, The Mills Music, Inc., c1953; proof copy (7 p.) (Box 25, Folder 876)
    arr. for organ by Virginia Carrington Thomas
    with manuscript Leroy Anderson note (1 p.)
  - Penny-Whistle Song, The (sketch), score (9 p.) (Box 25, Folder 877)
    holograph and copyist's manuscript
  - Penny-Whistle Song, The (sketch), condensed score (4 p.) (Box 25, Folder 878)
  - Phantom Regiment, The, 5/23/51; score (16 p.) (Box 13, Folder 447)
  - Phantom Regiment, The Mills Music Ltd., c1951; score (5 p.) (Box 13, Folder 448)
    English edition. 3 copies
  - Phantom Regiment, The Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (5 p.) (Box 13, Folder 449)
  - Phantom Regiment, The Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (5 p.) (Box 13, Folder 450)
  - Phantom Regiment, The Mills Music Inc., c1952; condensed score (5 p.) & parts (Box 13, Folder 451)
  - Phantom Regiment, The Mills Music Inc., c1952; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 13, Folder 452)
  - Phantom Regiment, The, 9/30/51; score (19 p.) (Box 25, Folder 879)
  - Phantom Regiment, The (sketch), 5/23/57; condensed score (4 p.) (Box 25, Folder 880)
  - Pirate Dance, 2/22/61; score (20 p.) (Box 13, Folder 453)
    Penciled corrections and additions included. "From the musical production 'Goldilocks'."
  - Pirate Dance Mills Music Inc., c1961; score (19 p.) (Box 13, Folder 454)
    male voices & piano
    "May be performed with symphonic band and symphonic orchestra editions." From the musical "Goldilocks." 3 copies.
  - Pirate Dance Mills Music Inc., c1961; score (19 p.) (Box 13, Folder 455)
    From the musical "Goldilocks." 4 copies.
  - Pirate Dance Ankerford Music Corporation, c1961; score (23 p.), condensed score (11 p.) & parts (Box 13, Folder 456)
  - Pirate Dance Ankerford Music Corporation, c1961; score (20 p.), condensed score (12 p.) & parts (Box 13, Folder 457)
  - Play Gypsies, Dance Gypsies, 1/30/49; condensed score (6 p.) (Box 13, Folder 458)
  - Play Some Music, score (5 p.) (Box 13, Folder 459)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (9 p.) & parts (Box 13, Folder 460)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Mills Music Inc., c1952 (Box 13, Folder 461)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk!, score (11 p.) (Box 13, Folder 462)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Mills Music Ltd., c1952; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 13, Folder 463)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Mills Music Ltd., c1955; score (5 p.) (Box 13, Folder 464)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Mills Music Ltd., c1952; score (5 p.) (Box 13, Folder 465)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Mills Music Ltd., c1952 (Box 13, Folder 466)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (7 p.) (Box 13, Folder 467)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Belwin Mills/Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (3 p.) & part (Box 13, Folder 468)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk!, c1952; condensed score (3 p.) & parts (Box 14, Folder 469)
    arr. Walter Dobschinski
    Edition Primus
    "Seitenstrasse" on reverse of all parts. German edition.
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (4 p.) (Box 14, Folder 470)
    "Professional copy."
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Mills Music, Belgium, c1952; score (4 p.) (Box 14, Folder 471)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (5 p.) (Box 14, Folder 472)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (7 p.) (Box 14, Folder 473)
  - Plink, Plank, Plunk! (sketch), 6/12/51; score (4 p.) (Box 25, Folder 881)
  - Polly Woddle Doodle - Fugue, score (7 p.) (Box 14, Folder 474)
    Mark Warnow
  - Pomp and Circumstance, score (3 p.) (Box 14, Folder 475)
  - Por Que "Chitarra Romana", 11/4/40; score (8 p.) (Box 14, Folder 476)
  - Portraits of Leroy Anderson, c1976; score (32 p.) (Box 14, Folder 477)
    arr. Chuck Cassey
    mixed voices & piano (optional guitar, bass, and drums)
    Collection of 6 compositions.
  - Precision, score (3 p.) (Box 14, Folder 478)
  - Prelude and Fugue in D Minor Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (22 p.) & parts (Box 14, Folder 479)
    G.F. Handel, trans. Hans Kindler
    Program notes by Leroy Anderson.
  - Princeton March, score (6 p.) (Box 14, Folder 480)
  - Promenade Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (11 p.) & parts (Box 14, Folder 481)
  - Promenade, score (20 p.) (Box 14, Folder 482)
    Pencil. "This is the original version played at the Boston Pops May 28, 1945 (Harvard Night) for the first time, then revised with a different coda for publication."
  - Promenade Mills Music Inc., 3/6/47; score (5 p.) (Box 14, Folder 483)
    2 pianos
  - Promenade Mills Music Ltd., c1949; score (7 p.) (Box 14, Folder 484)
  - Promenade Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (9 p.) (Box 14, Folder 485)
  - Promenade Mills Music Inc., c1953; parts (11 p.) (Box 14, Folder 486)
  - Promenade Mills Music Inc., c1949; score (7 p.) (Box 14, Folder 487)
  - Promenade Mills Music Inc., c1947; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 14, Folder 488)
    Includes manuscript drum parts (2).
  - Promenade, c1977; condensed score (12 p.) & parts (Box 14, Folder 489)
    arr. John Cacavas
  - Promenade, score (31 p.) (Box 24, Folder 806)
    Pencil and red pencil. Note on first page: (Revised) for print
  - Promenade, c1947, 1950; vocal score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 882)
    photocopy of copyist's score
  - Promenade (sketch), vocal score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 883)
  - Pussy Foot, The Ankerford Music Corp., c1958 (Box 14, Folder 490)
  - Pussy Foot, The Ankerford Music Corporation, 2/26/62; score (32 p.) (Box 14, Folder 491)
  - Pussy Foot, The Ankerford Music Corporation, c1958; score (5 p.) (Box 14, Folder 492)
  - Pyramid Dance, score (30 p.) (Box 14, Folder 493)
  - Pyramid Dance Mills Music Ltd., c1958; score (5 p.) (Box 14, Folder 494)
    English edition. From the musical "Goldilocks." 2 copies.
  - Pyramid Dance Ankerford Music Corporation, c1959; score (5 p.) (Box 14, Folder 495)
  - Pyramid Dance (Heart of Stone) Ankerford Music Corporation, c1960; score (31 p.), condensed score (12 p.) & parts (Box 14, Folder 496)
  - Pyramid Dance (Heart of Stone) Ankerford Music Corporation, c1960; score (31 p.), condensed score (12 p.) & parts (Box 15, Folder 497)
  - Pyramid Dance (Heart of Stone) Ashford Music Corp., 4/5/59; score (31 p.) (Box 25, Folder 884)
  - Quarter to Nine, score (7 p.) (Box 15, Folder 498)
  - Radcliffiana, condensed score (4 p.) (Box 15, Folder 499)
  - Rain Medley, score (4 p.) & parts (Box 15, Folder 500)
  - Rain Specialty, condensed score (1 p.) (Box 15, Folder 501)
  - Rakes of Mallow (from the "Irish Suite") (Box 24, Folder 807)
    score (27 leaves)
  - Rakes of Mallow, The Mills Music Inc., c1952; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 15, Folder 502)
  - Rakes of Mallow, The (sketch), condensed score (9 p.) (Box 25, Folder 885)
  - Reprise, score (3 p.) (Box 15, Folder 503)
  - Rhythmical Typewriter, The (sketch), condensed score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 886)
    typewriter & orchestra
  - Richard Rodgers Medley, part (7 p.) (Box 15, Folder 504)
    holograph (?)
    B flat tpt/sax/cl
  - Richard Rodgers Waltzes, 6/11/47; condensed score (12 p.) (Box 15, Folder 505)
  - Richard Rodgers Waltzes, 6/11/47; score (52 p.) (Box 24, Folder 808)
    Ink with pencil and red pencil additions. Note to printer laid in
  - Riff Song, score (3 p.) (Box 15, Folder 506)
  - Rio Rita, 2/27/49; (3 p.) (Box 15, Folder 507)
    condensed score
  - Roast Beef, Fresh Air, (2 p.) (Box 15, Folder 508)
  - Rosary, The, 1/30/1949; (2 p.) (Box 15, Folder 509)
  - Rose of the Rio Grande, score (1 p.) (Box 15, Folder 510)
  - Rosenkavalier Waltzes, score (11 p.) (Box 15, Folder 511)
    Pencil. Includes 1 p. piano sketch.
  - Saddle Your Blues to a Wild Mustang, 1/23/36; score (5 p.) (Box 15, Folder 512)
  - Sandpaper Ballet Mills Music Ltd., c1954; score (5 p.) (Box 15, Folder 513)
  - Sandpaper Ballet Mills Music Ltd., c1954; score (5 p.) (Box 15, Folder 514)
  - Sandpaper Ballet Mills Music Ltd., c1954; condensed score (7 p.) & parts (Box 15, Folder 515)
  - Sandpaper Ballet Mills Musikverlag, c1954; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 15, Folder 516)
    "Suzanne" on reverse of all parts. German edition.
  - Sandpaper Ballet Mills Music Inc., c1954; score (5 p.) (Box 15, Folder 517)
  - Sandpaper Ballet Mills Music Inc., c1954; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 15, Folder 518)
  - Sandpaper Ballet Mills Music Inc., c1954; condensed score (10 p.) & parts (Box 15, Folder 519)
  - Sandpiper Ballet, 11/22/54; score (19 p.) (Box 25, Folder 887)
  - Saraband, 1/4/48; score (18 p.) (Box 15, Folder 520)
  - Saraband Mills Music Ltd., c1954; condensed score (7 p.) & parts (Box 15, Folder 521)
  - Saraband Mills Music Ltd., c1950; score (7 p.) (Box 15, Folder 522)
  - Saraband Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (7 p.) (Box 15, Folder 523)
  - Saraband Mills Music Inc., c1959; score (7 p.) & parts (Box 15, Folder 524)
  - Saraband Mills Music Inc., c1959; parts (9 p.) (Box 15, Folder 525)
  - Saraband Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (7 p.) (Box 15, Folder 526)
  - Saraband Mills Music Inc., c1950; condensed score (6 p.) & parts (Box 16, Folder 527)
  - Saraband, 1/4/48; score (18 p.) (Box 24, Folder 809)
  - Saraband (sketch), score (2 p.) (Box 26, Folder 888)
    measures 1-8 only
  - Sarabande, c1955; score (4 p.) (Box 16, Folder 528)
  - Sarabande (sketch), condensed score (4 p.) (Box 26, Folder 889)
  - Save a Kiss, score (17 p.) & vocal part (Box 16, Folder 529)
    Pencil. Includes photocopy of vocal part. From the musical "Goldilocks."
  - Save a Kiss Ankerford Music Corporation, c1958; score (5 p.) (Box 16, Folder 530)
  - Schlager des Monats, c1965; score (11 p.) (Box 16, Folder 531)
    voice & accordion and/or piano
    Collection of 5 compositions including "Belle of the Ball" and "Blue Tango." German edition.
  - Second Dartmouth Medley, score (24 p.) (Box 16, Folder 532)
  - Second Regiment Connecticut National Guard March, score (18 p.) (Box 16, Folder 533)
    D.W. Reeves
  - Semper Fideles "National Emblem", 10/8/40; score (12 p.) (Box 16, Folder 535)
  - Serenade, 3/13/49; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 16, Folder 536)
  - Serenade (Schubert) (sketch), 3/26/67; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 26, Folder 890)
  - Serenade (Ständchen), score (14 p.) (Box 24, Folder 810)
    Schubert
    Ink with pencil additions. Note on cover: Ist performance May 2, 1967.
  - Serenade (Toselli) (sketch), condensed score (4 p.) (Box 26, Folder 891)
  - Serenade for Strings, score (5 p.) & vl part (Box 16, Folder 537)
  - Serenata Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (10 p.) & parts (Box 16, Folder 538)
  - Serenata, 2/12/47; score (20 p.) (Box 16, Folder 539)
  - Serenata Mills Music Ltd., c1950; score (4 p.) (Box 16, Folder 540)
  - Serenata Mills Music Ltd., c1949; score (8 p.) (Box 16, Folder 541)
  - Serenata Mills Music Ltd., c1950; score (5 p.) (Box 16, Folder 542)
  - Serenata Mills Music Inc., c1965; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 16, Folder 543)
    arr. Richard W. Bowles
  - Serenata Mills Music Inc., c1959; score (5 p.) & parts (Box 16, Folder 544)
  - Serenata Mills Music Inc., c1959; score (5 p.) & part (Box 16, Folder 545)
  - Serenata, c1981; score (7 p.) (Box 16, Folder 546)
    arr. Robert Ivey
  - Serenata Mills Musikverlag, c1956; score (3 p.) (Box 16, Folder 547)
  - Serenata, c1953; score (3 p.) (Box 16, Folder 548)
  - Serenata Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (4 p.) (Box 16, Folder 549)
  - Serenata, c1950; score (2 p.) (Box 16, Folder 550)
    Italian lyrics by Devilli-Cicero. Italian edition.
  - Serenata Mills Music Española, c1950; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 16, Folder 551)
    Music for "Hey, Mister Banjo!" on reverse side of all parts. Spanish edition.
  - Serenata Mills Music Española, c1953; Condensed score (3 p.) & parts (Box 16, Folder 552)
    Spanish lyrics by Rafael de León. Spanish edition.
  - Serenata Mills Music Española, c1953; score (4 p.) (Box 16, Folder 553)
    Spanish edition.
  - Serenata Editora Musical Mills Ltda., c1959; score (5 p.) (Box 16, Folder 554)
  - Serenata, c1950; score (3 p.) (Box 16, Folder 555)
    Editions Jacques Plante
  - Serenata Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (5 p.) (Box 16, Folder 556)
  - Serenata Mills Music Inc., c1954; score (9 p.) (Box 16, Folder 557)
  - Serenata Mills Music Inc., c1954; score (9 p.) (Box 16, Folder 558)
  - Serenata Mills Music Inc., c1949; condensed score (11 p.) & parts (Box 16, Folder 559)
  - Serenata, 1/31/50; score (35 p.) (Box 26, Folder 892)
  - Serenata (sketch), condensed score (8 p.) (Box 26, Folder 893)
  - Set for Love, 6/17/41; score (6 p.) (Box 16, Folder 560)
    Ernest Henderson
  - Seventy-six Trombones, score (24 p.) (Box 24, Folder 811)
    Meredith Willson
  - Seventy-Six Trombones (sketch), 4/6/58; condensed score (7 p.) (Box 26, Folder 894)
  - Shall I Take My Heart, 3/27/62; score (14 p.) (Box 16, Folder 561)
  - Shall I Take My Heart, score (11 p.) & vocal part (Box 16, Folder 562)
  - Shall I Take My Heart and Go? Mills Music Ltd., c1958; score (5 p.) (Box 16, Folder 563)
    English edition. 3 copies. From the musical "Goldilocks."
  - Shall We Dance, score (5 p.) (Box 16, Folder 564)
  - Showboat, score (52 p.) & parts (Box 17, Folder 565)
    Kern, Jerome
  - Showboat, score (52 p.) (Box 17, Folder 566)
  - Siboney, 4/10/49; condensed score (4 p.) (Box 17, Folder 567)
  - Simplified Arrangements for Piano Mills Music Ltd., c1961; score (18 p.) (Box 17, Folder 568)
    arr. Mark Stevens
  - Sing an Old Fashioned Song, 1/25/36; score (5 p.) (Box 17, Folder 569)
  - Slave Song, condensed score (1 p.) (Box 17, Folder 570)
  - Sleeping Beauty Waltz, score (9 p.) (Box 17, Folder 571)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (9 p.) (Box 16, Folder 534)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (8 p.) & parts (Box 17, Folder 572)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1950 (Box 17, Folder 573)
  - Sleigh Ride, c1948, 1950; score (15 p.) & parts (Box 17, Folder 574)
    arr. John Higgins
    Jenson Publications
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1962; score (3 p.) & parts (Box 17, Folder 575)
  - Sleigh Ride, c1980; score (12 p.) & parts (Box 17, Folder 576)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (29 p.) & parts (Box 18, Folder 577)
  - Sleigh Ride, 2/10/48; score (27 p.) (Box 18, Folder 578)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Ltd., c1948-1950; score (3 p.) & part (Box 18, Folder 579)
    French edition (titled "Promenade en Traineau.")
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Ltd., c1950; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 18, Folder 580)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Ltd., c1951; score (4 p.) (Box 18, Folder 581)
    English edition for children. 4 copies.
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Ltd., c1951; score (7 p.) (Box 18, Folder 582)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Ltd., c1950; score (4 p.) (Box 18, Folder 583)
    chorus & piano
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Ltd., c1950; score (7 p.) (Box 18, Folder 584)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Ltd., c1948; score (7 p.) (Box 18, Folder 585)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Ltd., c1950 (Box 18, Folder 586)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Ltd., c1953; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 18, Folder 587)
  - Sleigh Ride Toa Music Company, c1975 T.V. Asahi Music; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 18, Folder 588)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1962; score (6 p.) (Box 18, Folder 589)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1957; score (9 p.) (Box 18, Folder 590)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (2 p.) (Box 18, Folder 591)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (5 p.) (Box 18, Folder 592)
    Children's edition.
  - Sleigh Ride, c1977; score (12 p.) (Box 18, Folder 593)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1965; score (7 p.) (Box 18, Folder 594)
    voice & organ
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (5 p.) (Box 18, Folder 595)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (4 p.) (Box 18, Folder 596)
    "Professional Copy."
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1957; parts (11 p.) (Box 18, Folder 597)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Musikverlag, c1955; score (4 p.) (Box 18, Folder 598)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (4 p.) (Box 18, Folder 599)
    piano (or ukulele)
    "Professional copy." 2 copies.
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Belgium, c1950; score (3 p.) (Box 18, Folder 600)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1949; score (7 p.) (Box 18, Folder 601)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1963; parts (8 p.) (Box 18, Folder 602)
    arr. Pietro Deiro, Jr.
    accordion ensemble
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (7 p.) (Box 18, Folder 603)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (15 p.) (Box 18, Folder 604)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1958; score (10 p.) (Box 18, Folder 605)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (15 p.) (Box 18, Folder 606)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1962; score (15 p.) (Box 18, Folder 607)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1950; score (15 p.) (Box 18, Folder 608)
  - Sleigh Ride Mills Music Inc., c1948; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 18, Folder 609)
  - Sleigh Ride (Passeio de Treno) Editora Musical Mills Ltda., c1959; score (7 p.) (Box 18, Folder 610)
  - Sleigh Ride (Promenade en Traineau) Mills Music Belgium, c1950; score (3 p.) (Box 18, Folder 611)
    French lyrics by Jacques Plante. 2 copies.
  - Sleigh Ride (sketch), score (1 p.) (Box 26, Folder 895)
  - Sleigh Ride (Slee Rit) Mills Music Belgium, c1950; score (2 p.) (Box 18, Folder 612)
    Dutch lyrics by Erik Franssen-Van Aleda.
  - Sleigh Ride (Sulla Slitta) Music Union Milano, c1950; score (3 p.) (Box 18, Folder 613)
    Italian lyrics by Spiker. Italian edition.
  - Sleigh Ride/Serenata Mills Musikverlag, c1955; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 18, Folder 614)
  - Society Rag, score (2 p.) (Box 19, Folder 615)
    Pencil. Attached to "Zigeuner."
  - Softly as in a Morning Service, 2/6/49; condensed score (4 p.) (Box 19, Folder 616)
  - Soldier's Field, score (4 p.) (Box 19, Folder 617)
  - Someday, score (4 p.) (Box 19, Folder 618)
  - Song Is You, The, 5/15/49; condensed score (4 p.) (Box 19, Folder 619)
  - Song of Jupiter Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (5 p.) & parts (Box 19, Folder 620)
    G.F. Handel
  - Song of Jupiter Mills Music Inc., score (15 p.) (Box 19, Folder 621)
  - Song of Jupiter Mills Music Inc., c1954; score (10 p.) (Box 19, Folder 622)
  - Song of Jupiter Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (15 p.) & parts (Box 19, Folder 623)
  - Song of Jupiter, 7/5/51; score (15 p.) (Box 26, Folder 896)
  - Song of Songs, 3/20/49; condensed score (2 p.) (Box 19, Folder 624)
  - Song of the Bells Mills Music Inc., c1955; score (23 p.) & parts (Box 19, Folder 625)
  - Song of the Bells Mills Music Inc., c1954; score (7 p.) (Box 19, Folder 626)
  - Song of the Bells Mills Music Inc., c1958; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 19, Folder 627)
  - Song of the Bells, 2/28/55; score (30 p) (Box 26, Folder 897)
  - Song of the Bells (sketch), condensed score (10 p.) (Box 26, Folder 898)
  - Songs of Dartmouth, condensed score (10 p.) (Box 19, Folder 628)
  - Sooner or Later, score (3 p.) (Box 19, Folder 629)
  - South Pacific Selections, condensed score (15 p.) (Box 19, Folder 630)
  - South Pacific Selections, score (60 p.) (Box 24, Folder 812)
    Stamp on first page: Registered 1949
    ink with pencil and red pencil additions.
  - Southern Roses, score (10 p.) (Box 19, Folder 631)
  - Spanish Dance, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 19, Folder 632)
  - Specialty, score (2 p.) (Box 19, Folder 633)
  - Still of the Night, score (7 p.) (Box 19, Folder 634)
  - Stouthearted Men, 2/20/49; condensed score (4 p.) (Box 19, Folder 635)
  - Strange Music, 1/2/49; condensed score (4 p.) (Box 19, Folder 636)
  - Street Scene, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 19, Folder 637)
  - Suite of Carols Mills Music Inc., c1955; score (23 p.) & parts (Box 19, Folder 638)
  - Suite of Carols Mills Music Inc., c1955; score (23 p.) (Box 19, Folder 639)
    "Corrected copy."
  - Suite of Carols Mills Music Inc., c1955; score (31 p.) & parts (Box 19, Folder 640)
    brass choir
  - Suite of Carols Mills Music Inc., c1955; score (23 p.) & parts (Box 19, Folder 641)
    woodwind ensemble
    "Corrected copy" of score also.
  - Suite of Carols, score (37 p.) (Box 19, Folder 642)